[Music]
[Applause]
South Boston, St. Patrick's Day.
Our Father who art in heaven,
Hallowed be thy name, come to
we your kingdom, your will be done
on earth as it is in heaven. Give us
today is our daily bread and forgive
our offenses as well as we
We forgive those who offend us. We do not
do not fall into temptation
and deliver us from evil.
For yours is the kingdom, the power and the
gloria
now and forever.
Amen.
Thank you, Father Mlepen, for coming from
the other side of town to see
our guest speaker.
Thanks for inviting me.
When I lift my shining sword
and my fist takes hold of my judgment,
I will take revenge on all my enemies.
Those who hate me will get what they deserve.
Mister,
Seat me at your right hand and hold me as one
of your saints.
[Music]
And on this holy day I remember the sad
history
de Kitty Chenop.
As you all remember,
a long time ago, almost 30 years,
That poor soul cried out for help once
and again, but no one answered his
supplications.
Although many saw it, no one
He didn't even call the police.
Everyone watched as Kitty was stabbed.
to death in broad daylight.
They watched as their attacker walked away.
walking.
Well, we should all fear men.
wicked,
But there is another kind of evil to which we owe
fear more.
Forks
indifference
of good men.
I think the monsignor finally got it.
understood.
Yeah.
[Music]
Understand,
That
[Applause]
[Music]
who rules here?
Yes, of course. They're going to instruct him today.
Dog.
[Music]
The rule of thumb or the base
the rule of thumb.
At the beginning of the 20th century it was legal to
men will mistreat their wives
while using a stick no wider than
his thumb.
You can't do much harm with this.
Maybe it should have been the rule of the wrist.
I knew you idiots would bring me
problems. Come on. It's St. Patrick's Day, it's a
fun day.
Rot and rot you too.
Oh, excuse us. It's okay. Relax.
Oh, God.
The fifth hell.
Spanish version. Gigabox.
[Music]
David de la Rocó, Italian mafia of
Boston, Ycabeta family, position
messenger, bookmaker.
[Music]
Hey, idiot, give me a beer.
[Laughs]
Listen, listen, guys. I have very
bad news.
I'll have to close the bar. The Russians
They are buying buildings all over the
city, including this one. [ __ ]
And they won't let me renew the rent.
Let me talk to my boss. Yes, maybe he
can do. What [ __ ] do you think is going to happen?
to be? And listen carefully. I don't want you to
Nobody knows, so don't open your mouth.
You know what they say. With a closed mouth.
crows don't enter.
Hey, Doc, I have to buy you a book.
of proverbs or something like that because this thing
confusing them must end.
A gift horse. Fine, thank you.
And don't cross the road if you don't leave
the kitchen.
I'm Ivan Cheekov and you're going to close.
now.
Ivan Cheekov, Russian mafia, position
soldier.
Checco. Good,
This is MY. If we find a Spock,
there is a full team.
I'm not in the mood to argue. You, you
you stay, the others leave.
Why don't you just listen to him and be
get out of here, [ __ ]
Calm down.
Do you know that we have until the end of the
week? No, they don't have to be so hard,
TRUE?
It's Saint Patrick's Day.
We are all Irish today. Sit down and
drink with us.
This is not a game.
If they don't leave, we'll make them leave.
The next day murder in the street and
avenue requests police presence
immediate.
Careful.
These two were killing each other.
One of them took a sink or something
like that and crushed the other's head. He did
a loud noise. Someone had to
having heard it. So immediately
appeared a little large. Then he pushed
and jumped on him. But the bastard
I actually wanted to steal,
that is, he took advantage of the situation,
committed the attraction and the whitest.
Agent Pulsmecker FBI, counterterrorism unit
racketeering.
Do you understand? He escaped. Look at him. He has the
broken back. It had to be a
big wretch weighing up to 200 kg. A
huge guy.
That is hardly credible.
Very little.
Attention all units.
Okay, fine. Let's say these two
guys didn't even know the
big bastard. They came out drunk
from a bar on St. Patrick's Day.
Last night. They decide to take a shortcut through this
alley.
Very bad decision.
Because the big guy was waiting for them.
Yes. What could be more perfect for a
robbery like that? Two drunk guys, all
bandaged, they were already wounded. Look at them.
These guys were doing
The big guy took an object and then
hit the guy with his bandaged head.
Yes. And why? Because he's smart. He knows
that the guy with the bandaged butt doesn't
will go anywhere. Of course it won't go anywhere.
Nowhere. Where are you going? Nowhere.
side.
Exact.
But it's not over yet. He came here and jumped.
on this guy's back.
crushed him to death.
This is something important.
I wouldn't be surprised if more appeared.
cases.
Bright.
Now we have the big guy theory and
the serial crusher. First class.
Who are you,
Detective Greenley? Who [ __ ] is
you?
Here's who [ __ ] I am.
Listen, I have to follow the rules.
We just identified them.
They have connections to the Russian mafia. That's it.
makes them a federal case. The
SMER agent will lead the investigation
with our total.
Why don't you bring me some good coffee?
What the hell is it? Coffee with milk. A
boss shell. What the [ __ ] is this? and
sweetener. Yes.
Yeah,
they call.
[Music]
My story is short
to you
embroidery at home and away
I'm calm.
[Music]
margin
ros
[Music]
I like
those
things
how sweet Maria
[Music]
they talk about
Reait
[Music]
Mitchell Langly. Yes, sir.
Find the manager of this building.
See if anyone has complained about leaks
in any of the departments from
this morning. Llangle, take care of that
building. Same.
Saify
Newman.
Yes sir.
Look for trash around you. See if
finds two bullet cartridges. Caliber
50. If my eyesight doesn't fail me.
Newman, check this garbage.
If they used a sink,
find metal parts, find the
drain plug, a faucet or whatever.
Here I have it. 50 caliber.
Chief, bring ballistics here. Tell them that
They have to pull a bullet out of the wall
50 caliber and find another one that
went through the trash can.
The world's leading ballistics expert
will be here in 10 minutes.
And how did you know?
For liquid.
Positive self
and bullet holes are a good
track.
No one heard any gunshots.
It's an Irish neighborhood. I'm surprised.
that they even called them.
Sir, can't find the second one.
Look, under the body.
Ah, yes, there it is.
Ready for my theory?
It was not a murder by rival gangs,
Although it is original. It is too
neglected. Something went wrong here. Without
doubt was a personal matter.
Agent Smaker, all these homes are
illegal. There is no one in charge. But
A lady on the fourth floor said that she
water fell and flooded the entire house.
It started this morning.
Fourth floor.
So let's go up to the fifth.
Come on. What are we doing here? It's crazy.
It's a theory.
I don't know. Impossible. You know how big it is.
must be to do that more than
huge.
Really? Maybe I want a donut.
with coffee.
I won't bring you a [ __ ] donut.
You'll be the first to kiss my ass.
you.
Agent Smaker. Agent. Wait. Hey,
I know this neighborhood very well. There is a
bar further on called Mintlis. It's very
They were probably there last night.
Good work, Mit. I'll go check it out myself.
same.
Look at the ceiling. Use your cue. Wait for it.
move.
Uh. So fast you didn't even feel it,
TRUE?
Again, again, again. Look at the
roof. Uh,
Thanks for coming, Doc.
Good heavens, what the [ __ ] happened?
Are you okay?
We're alive. An FBI agent came to the
bar. He left me his He left me his
He left me his card. [ __ ]
What are they going to do?
Let's surrender. It was in defense.
own.
Yes, yes, yes. That's what he said.
How does [ __ ] know? We haven't talked yet.
with no one.
I don't know. He didn't tell me.
Okay. Listen, Doc. We need a
favor.
Whatever.
Yes. Keep this. We'll get it back.
when it is
[ __ ]
of the father of the
None of those swear words were directed at
to you. He's a little touched.
Boston Police.
First of all
I want to thank the smartest one
among you, great doughnut eater,
with a huge ass and a huge idiot
who leaked this to the press.
Just what we needed.
sensationalist article in the
newspapers that portray these types
like superheroes triumphing over the
bad. I'll stop the rumors now.
These two are not heroes,
They are just two ordinary men who
They found themselves in an unusual and
by chance they came out on top.
Yes, our advanced computer system
found nothing about the two of them. Just
We know what we found out from the
neighbors and the general opinion is
that they are angels,
but angels do not kill.
And we have two bodies in the morgue that
They appear to have been crushed by a
damn gigantic guy.
We consider them armed and dangerous.
Well, not armed. If they had weapons,
They would have used them. Dangerous, for sure.
Why do you think they are dangerous? Maybe
They only protected each other.
And, listen, I'm not saying one thing or the other,
just be careful and follow the
regulation.
This will require a great effort
police officer.
Those guys are already far away from here,
But if you want to smash your head,
I'll tell you what you're looking for. You're afraid.
like two helpless bunnies. Any
uniformed or patrol will scare them.
agreed? So the only thing we can do is
to do is hang a potato from a thread and
drag her through South Boston.
Thank you for coming.
I'd have better luck with a beer.
Yes, it is true.
Good heavens!
He Greenly. Onion donut with
cream cheese.
This conversation will be recorded.
Just answer what you really need.
Excuse me, sir, please.
Okay, we're ready.
Know that you are not under oath here,
Just answer the questions. I guess.
that they knew them from before, eh,
we met them last night.
They had some very interesting bandages.
Do you know anything about that?
Hey, if you want to fight, you'll see that
are at a disadvantage. We want to be
civilized, so accept our
offer.
I make the offers.
Hey, Boris.
What would you do if I told you that
your [ __ ] communist mother sucks so many
penises that look like
Bo on the role.
Leave him alone, he can defend himself.
[Music]
Yes, pray. Fire.
[Applause]
Quiet down, you damn Irish, [ __ ]
Get up, [ __ ] Come on,
let me go at once.
Put on the handcuffs from behind.
Put them on.
Let's go.
Do you know why the fuck I'm here? I came
to kill you,
but now I think I won't kill you.
I'll kill your brother. I'll shoot his
head.
Die.
We have to go.
No no,
It was just a [ __ ] bar fight. They are some
cowards.
[Applause]
Hope
[Music]
that you have a clear conscience and
large
[Music]
is seeing,
seeing.
[Music]
AND
[Applause]
[Music]
How come they speak Russian fluently?
Well, we pay attention in school.
Do you speak any other languages?
Yes, our mother insisted on that.
French.
marvelous.
It's not the slightest idea.
Bravo.
working in a [ __ ] packing plant
meat.
Agents
Yeah,
The press is everywhere. They are
like crazy about them. What do I do?
They have no charges. Decide. Do you want
talk to them?
Of course.
And without photos.
Can we stay here?
Ah, yes. We have an extra cell that
they can
can stay.
We'll ask your mom.
For me there is no problem if your friends
they sleep here.
[Laughs]
Time to feed the dogs.
One question, boss.
Sir, this way.
Okay, everyone listen up. This is our
official statement.
The McManus brothers were not charged.
of the crime.
It is a clear case of self-defense.
They will be released in a moment.
and secret places such as
requested. The McManus brothers have
background. Can we talk to them?
Where are you? One question. Answer.
Can you give us any other information?
Hey, Roco, how are you?
Hey, hello.
Yeah,
friend.
What do you have there?
That poor soul cried out for help.
They watched as their attacker walked away.
walking. The indifference of the
good men. Nobody wanted
get involved. Nobody. Nobody. Nobody.
Shed the blood of man.
For man his blood will be shed.
For in the image of God he is made
man.
destroy everything that is evil
so that everything that is good may flourish.
[Music]
What's that?
It's the damn Russian's viper.
Okay, let's go.
Good morning, guys. How are you?
Good morning.
Keep the faith, brother.
Suck it.
Give me a pen.
Yes, yes. What's wrong?
Thanks. I'll be right back.
Good morning. How are you? Hello.
It would be an honor if you would join us.
Did you see this?
the South Boston Saints?
The Saints.
Christ of
President.
Comedian. Give me that, messenger.
Joy Vivo said it was important. I must
give it to him myself.
Give me that [ __ ] thing.
Sit down, [ __ ]
Bichen Solapsi, second chief. Family
Ycabeta. I'm Roco, I'm the comedian.
I'm so funny.
Don't bother me anymore, Vincho.
And that black eye? What's wrong? Don't you
Did you seem funny to anyone?
Yusepi Yacabeta, alias Papa Joe, head of
the mafia, Ycabeta family.
I saw your show at the Velvet Room in
Hollyin. I loved it when you sang Viva.
Las Vegas.
Ah, I'm going to kill you, huh? You play with me.
rotting for hours. You're a
damn stupid insignificant, [ __ ]
I always get my money, asshole.
bastard.
The 90s are killing me. It wasn't supposed to be.
that. You should no longer tell someone that
You're going to kill him. I have to handle myself with
be very careful with these idiots.
They took all the fun out of it.
To my work.
Papa Jo wants me to leave.
The boys tell me that they laugh a lot
when you come. What do you have? A lot
grace. What do they call you?
The comedian.
I'm having a day, Pes. I'm
Depressed. Tell me a nice joke.
now.
A joke. Ah,
a joke. Yes, agreed. It turns out that
There are three types.
A Latin
a white man and a brown man
negro.
Yes, yes. And they walk along the beach and
They see a lamp and rub it. The
genie and tells them to make the wish that
want. He asks the Mexican what
wants and he tells her, "I want everyone
my countrymen in the United States live
happy and free in Mexico." And the genius
goes puff and all the Latinos go back to
Mexico. And then he asks the dark-skinned man,
"¿Negro?"
Yes, that's what I said. Then he asks the
black, says to him, "Hey, what do you want?"
If the black man says, "I want all my
Africans, my black brothers in
The United States returns to Africa and is
happy and free." Well, then the
Genius goes puff and all the blacks in
The United States is returning to Africa. This is not
It's going today. I'm not funny, I know. I'm
having a bad day. This joke sucks.
It's a stupid joke, sir.
Keep telling it.
So the genie asks the white man,
"What is your wish?" And the white one says,
"So all blacks and Latinos
were from the United States?" The genius
says, "Yeah." And he says, "Well, give me one
Coca then.
[Laughs]
Give me a Coke. Give me a Coke.
Give me a Coke.
Yes. Yes. They're both gone, so just
wants a Coke. It's the only thing
needs.
[Music]
Tell me another one.
That?
Have fun.
[Music]
When the wicked are confused,
call me with the saints around.
Damn!
Know
[Music]
what we need?
Some strings.
Of course. Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy. Charlie Bronson always
has a rope.
That?
Yes. I carry a rope with him in the
movies and I always end up using it.
You've lost your mind, haven't you? I'm
speaking very seriously.
Don't be stupid. What are you going to do?
need a rope?
You never know what you'll need it for,
but it is always needed.
This is real life, it's not a
movie.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Look who's talking. Rambo,
okay. Take your [ __ ] and stupid
rope.
I'm going to take my stupid rope. I'll go for it.
she.
Here's my rope. Hey?
[Music]
Are
highly strung?
A little bit too.
Hello,
Mhm. Room number
and the time of death.
Do we know how many dead?
Dog.
I'll be there soon. Keep the press away.
What were you doing?
I just wanted to cuddle.
Seriously, what [ __ ]
Uh,
This is a [ __ ] butcher shop.
How many bodies are there, Green Lee?
Eight.
Oh, [ __ ] I forgot about that one. Nine.
Nine. Since Greenly is going for coffee,
Does anyone else want anything?
Good heavens.
GOOD,
Do you have any theories that match with
that tie?
Look, at [ __ ] all these guys. This
was his goal, the [ __ ]
What did you say?
The fat guy.
Wow, Freud was right. So you think
who wanted to kill the [ __ ]
What do you base this on?
He's the only one they killed for sure.
Two shots in the back of the head, a new thug
who leaves his signature.
Two solid theories in one day and none
is related to big men.
I feel like dancing.
Another possibility is that they placed them
there with religious intentions.
Okay. Some cultures still place
pennies in the eyes of the dead or
payment.
The Italians, the Greeks,
the Sicilians.
Well, what is the symbolism here?
The symbology.
Now that Dafy has renounced the crown of
idiot king, we already have an heir
throne. Surely the word you wanted
use was symbolism. What is the
symbolism here? I'll explain it to you.
In Greek and Roman mythology,
you had to pay the toll to die
Charon, the ferryman who took you to
through the gates of judgment. Thus
They ensured that the dead atoned
the sins committed in life. Detective
the Warm Pops.
Gosh, you're the first to say that.
GOOD.
Yes, well, I'm an expert in nombrology.
The two bullets entered through here through
from the crown, they crossed and
came out through the eyes. This clue gives us
says three very different things.
First, Dafy,
He was shot aiming down.
they knelt down.
Excellent. Second, Greenly.
He was shot aiming down the road.
He tells us that he was the last to die.
Third, Dolly.
Ah, there were two traitors.
More than fantastic.
One moment.
Follow me, guys. What did you do for
inflict two identical wounds? Two
men of similar height put it
on their knees. Each one pointed his
gun and boom, end of story.
What if it was a guy with two guns?
Possible, but unlikely. The angles
are very extreme. A man holding
two guns on the back of the head would shoot towards
forward. I wouldn't lean my elbows like that. No
makes sense. Besides, you tell me that a
one guy came in here and killed eight
men with accurate shots in just
a few seconds. Impossible.
There were at least two.
[Music]
You and your [ __ ] rope.
I told him there would be a gap, just like
on TV.
Yuri Petroba, Russian mafia, position boss.
[Music]
[Applause]
We're just standing there
[Music]
where [ __ ] you are going.
I hear voices out there. [ __ ] I am
sweating like a motherfucker carrying your
[ __ ] rope. It must weigh 15 kilos. What
We're doing this very seriously. Now calm down,
[ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] I'm not the one who knows
Charlie Brons believes and doesn't know where he's going.
Shut up once and for all,
son of [ __ ] mother.
Wait,
[ __ ]
[Music]
We will be shepherds for you, my Lord, for
everything. From your hand you granted us the
power. That we may carry out your orders
quickly. A river will flow to you
that will always be packed with soul. In
the name of the Father, Father, of the Son and
of the Holy Spirit.
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
And I will include them among my sheep
favorites
and will have the protection of all
the angels of heaven.
Television.
Television is the explanation for this.
It's like a TV movie.
Small attackers crawling by
ducts, entering through the roof. The thing about
James Bond does not happen in reality. The
professionals don't do that.
Tell me, why would you need one?
stupid and [ __ ] sane? Huh,
that was much easier than
I expected.
On TV you always have that guy who
jumps over the couch. You shoot him
for 10 [ __ ] minutes.
[ __ ] we are good.
Of course.
Hey, what do you think is in that?
briefcase?
[ __ ]
This work just keeps getting better.
Smell, smell. I love the new job.
Unfortunate,
they gave him his big chance.
Let's fuck it up. What do you think?
Want?
Okay.
You open the door, I'll hold it.
hair.
Come here.
Lower your head.
Don't shoot, don't shoot. Close the
[ __ ] please.
Get on the floor. Now.
Don't shoot. We're on the same side.
They only sent me as reinforcement. I am
Roco. I'm the comedian, but it's not my
name. I say I'm the comedian. By
Please. Here it is. Yes, yes, yes. That's not it
my real name.
That [ __ ] [ __ ]
You only have six [ __ ] bullets.
[ __ ] There are nine bodies. Genius.
What [ __ ] were you thinking of doing? Killing
laughter at the last three comedians.
Papa Joe said there were only two of them. Come in.
and leave.
Wow, they did a great job.
Ah, [ __ ] They're good, huh? Pretty
masks. Where did they get them?
We have to kill him right here.
No,
right now.
No, no, no. Please, please don't.
kill me. I'm the comedian. I'm the comedian. By
Please don't kill me.
I'm the comedian.
[Laughs]
He's an idiot.
Damn! What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] Who [ __ ] to [ __ ] this,
how [ __ ] did [ __ ] [ __ ]
Well, that illustrates the diversity of the
word.
All these guys are from the Russian mafia,
but not like those pawns in the alley
from the other day. These guys are the
top bosses and second bosses. I have a
file on every man in this
room.
Since the end of the Iron Curtain,
Russian mafias started coming here.
In the spirit of Glasnuts, the
Soviets opened their borders to the
mafia, but the Italians are not
convinced that Russia is a land
fertile for organized crime, as well
who do not want to commit. But the
Russians are coming here anyway
forms and are not welcome.
So what we have here, gentlemen,
It is possibly the beginning of the
first international mafia war,
unless I've missed something.
Live from the Copy Plaza Hotel,
where we have just been informed that it happened
the largest mass murder in the
Boston history. We learned that there was
nine victims, all closely linked to
a very Russian mafia organization
violent right here in Boston.
anyone they think is evil, or
sea,
Don't you find it a little strange, a little
Crazy? You know what I think is crazy? Roco
They are decent men with families,
They come home from work and put the
news. And what do they see? They see rapists,
to murderers and pedophiles,
everyone getting out of jail, mobsters.
those who are caught with 20 kg coming out
on bail for the same damn day. And
everywhere everyone thinks
equal
that someone should kill those
bastards.
Kill them all.
Admit it,
even you thought so.
They should be in the cities
important.
This is very serious.
This is like the lone ranger.
To [ __ ] There is so much [ __ ] that makes me
anger.
They should draft me because I'm fed up,
[ __ ] of walking down the street
waiting for one of those drug addicts
miserable and damned poroseros me
attack.
Hallelujah. Jafar,
They're not just talking about mobsters, are they?
They talk about pimps, traffickers and everything
that, right?
Oh,
[ __ ] They could do this every damn time
day.
We are like those stores,
they don't always work.
But they are always open.
Very well said. Thank you very much.
[Music]
I'll make mincemeat out of you.
So we came in through the roof like this
straining the door
and then
[Music]
they are bastards.
They ruined me.
I'm finished.
I will always be a poor messenger.
Who says that? Can you say that?
did you do?
Are you serious?
And you can't go back there?
and tell him it was us?
You'll move up a ladder, my friend.
Don Roco.
I'm going to do it. I deserve it. I've been doing it.
working for those wretches since
high school. Look at this damn
place. They make fun of me, old man. So
those bastards can suck my pathetic
little tail. I won't even dip my eggs in the sauce.
of marinara so that the [ __ ] bastards
can taste a little bit of Italy.
[ __ ] I will. Yes, sir.
For God's sake,
my god, my god. [ __ ] dier. [ __ ]
That [ __ ]
I can't believe what just happened.
He's dead.
Oh my God.
Don will be very happy for the cat.
[ __ ]
He takes so many drugs that he won't realize
account. I would have sold the cat in exchange
of a few coins,
but I still feel like an idiot.
Yes, Rock, you sound so sorry.
I haven't seen her for weeks at all.
forms.
Listen, there is something that does worry me about
last night.
That?
What if your boss did know how many
was there? What are you? What are you
saying?
Just think about it. Nine men, six
bullets. Do you think it was a trap? No,
old. Impossible.
Listen, listen. Maybe he knew that
you would kill that fat man, maybe several
more, but I knew you wouldn't get out alive
there. With the killer dead at the scene.
They weren't going to investigate. He would be free.
of suspicion.
So what [ __ ] I love you
A lot, my friend. But you're not exactly
don Corleone.
No, no, that's not how they do things.
Also, how did he know I would get in? And if
He saw that there were many, he served him his [ __ ]
food and I was leaving
knows Rojo. A professional would come in,
would see that it is impossible and then
I would leave, but for you it was your only
chance.
You waited 18 [ __ ] years.
No, no, no, no. That, that, that's not it. No,
That's it, it's a lie. You don't know what
you're saying. Things aren't like that.
I mean, thanks for caring, but like this
is not the point.
Yes, yes, whatever you want. Do me a favor.
Yes. Think about it a little bit the other way around. No, no,
I'm not going to think about it. I shouldn't think about
nothing.
[ __ ]
Where are you going? Did you tell him?
Of course I told him.
So what [ __ ]
The truth is that you don't know one thing
[ __ ]
You're an [ __ ] idiot, you know?
Hey, fuck off.
So, use your [ __ ] brain for a
time. Does it seem so incredible to you that they don't
amounts of [ __ ]
You [ __ ] Irish, you know everything,
What?
[ __ ] mother, you shouldn't risk it with
this, do you understand?
I'm getting out of here.
Okay, [ __ ] What flowers do you want in your
funeral, idiot? This is the last time you
I'll see.
I'll be back at 9. Throw in the [ __ ] cat.
Hey, if you go in there you feel a bad feeling
vibrate, just get off your ass and go.
Hello,
are you OK?
Someone called me.
No, I'm sure you're okay.
I'm fine.
We'll see each other later.
[Laughs]
Come on, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Take your things. Take your things.
We must go. We must go.
Hey, what the hell are you talking about?
I killed them. God, I killed them all.
Calm down! Just tell us what happened. Roco,
calm down, friend.
Damn! They better start
move, you bastards. We must go.
Roco,
Roco, what [ __ ] Who did you kill?
How much did he know?
Aporesis, [ __ ]
And, wait.
Very good. I love this [ __ ] What [ __ ]
What's wrong with you, friend?
Those bastards betrayed me.
I told you, Rock. They tried to kill you.
What the hell am I going to do? It was right in
Lake View.
Lake View. The Rock Cafe. It seems that
we have a new recruit.
That?
And my cat.
I killed your [ __ ] cat, you drug addict bitch.
God, why?
Because I thought that would put an end to
our relationship.
You killed me. My
You what,
me
You what, [ __ ] Hey, you what, bitch.
I'll shoot myself in the head if you can.
tell me the name of that cat. Go ahead.
You what, your dearest what.
Oh, God. And what color was it, bitch?
Don't yell at him like that, you idiot.
Shut your [ __ ] mouth, Raby. I can't
buy some [ __ ] cigarettes without
run into nine guys with whom
you took. [ __ ] [ __ ] be.
Come on, let's go. Let's go quickly.
Those damn rats were all laughing
of me.
Are you sure you killed them?
I believe it, [ __ ] I didn't leave one alive
in that place. Did someone call me?
No, I'm sure you're okay.
I'm fine.
We'll see each other a little later.
[Music]
I know something happen in here.
It was certainly a [ __ ] test.
Bienenzo came here talking like a
parrot. He made sure we knew,
but we did what we had to do.
We kept our mouths shut.
You, uh, you did your part.
[ __ ] Now they know that we are from the
family.
We take good care of this.
What? Everyone knew. You're going to tell me.
that Sal knew it too.
Vincenzo told Sal first. That
bastard knew it before.
At least we have the comedian back.
That was funny, wasn't it? It was really
funny, isn't it?
Funny. Funny. Very funny.
Damn dog. Very funny.
[Music]
Listen, Rock. Did anyone see you?
Damn! Many people are hanging from a fence.
posters. I did it in public.
Liberating, right?
Let's go, [ __ ]
Do you know a little? Yes.
Coner, stop the car. Stop the [ __ ]
auto.
Vincenzo. That damn bastard, the hand
Yacabeta's right is the one who extended me
the trap and then told everyone that
I was a dead man. Here comes the
Wednesday night at 10.
always masturbates with a stripper,
never fails.
And?
So what? Let's kill that bastard. I mean, what
Are you? Aren't you doing that now?
Yes. Good.
Ah, what [ __ ] I mean, whose turn is it?
Are you doing a raffle or something?
Well, if the truth be told,
we don't choose them first.
So what do they do?
We don't have a system to decide
who. Rook is.
I will serve them. I know everyone.
world, its habits, its friends, with
Who are they talking to, I have their numbers
phones, addresses, I know who to talk to
they lie down and I know where they live.
We can kill them all.
What do you think?
It sounds weird, but I like it.
It's him.
[Music]
Okay.
What? You guys have masks on.
You look like a cartoon character.
Okay. Something to watch out for. When we're done
that I identify with, I don't care. Just
I try to be professional, but no.
[ __ ] Shut up, [ __ ] Do you look okay?
Put that on. Now, you're scary, man.
Let's go.
Listen, Rock, are you sure? But very
sure you're ready.
She was here when it all happened.
He recognized them.
No
They wore masks.
Of course.
If you scream I'll kill you. Which one is it in? And no
pretend you don't know who I'm talking to
talking.
You don't have to talk to me like that,
dirty little girl.
Almost no.
What a disgusting bastard.
How many?
Three. And two of them fired.
So it should be in the name of the Father,
of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
Our theory of night has just gone
al [ __ ]
This is something new.
After talking to the stripper,
We know that they wanted to kill the one in the
middle cabin.
After seeing how they killed him,
fainted. Why are there two victims?
Witnesses.
No, they couldn't see it.
Let me explain, gentlemen,
the industry protocol
pornographic, as I'm sure that
never been to a place like this.
A guy walks into a booth, puts in money
through the slot, the stripper picks it up
on the other side, press the button and the
door goes up. They are only separated by the
crystal and it's time to give it to
Firefighter.
It's impossible that they could see it.
The doors were down. That
means that
They looked inside through the
peepholes, they saw these guys. They opened
the doors from the inside. Bam, bam,
pam, through the glass.
Because?
It's a board of perverts.
We should clean once a day.
week.
Maybe the three subjects had something in
common.
No, this guy is a big shot. These two
are scarce.
That's what they had in common. All three were guys
bad guys. Now they're dead bad guys.
Come on, let me finish him off. I know I'm a
imbecile. I have to make up for what I did
forget it with them. I waited a long time for this one
moron.
Come on,
Come on, man. Give it a chance.
This is serious, Rock. Bad men,
dead men.
Good aim,
bad aim.
[Music]
Besides,
we have a real theory in the style
of Kennedy's assassination. Here they used
two guns. The guy in the middle was killed
with both, but this guy was killed
with the bullets from the gun Nothing more and
this one with those of gun B. But
Ballistics removed two bullets from the wall
the B here, where the victim was
murdered with the A. And the same thing happens
here.
Why do they cross?
That's very strange. I have no idea.
God, I can't think anymore. The scene
at the cafeteria today I was exhausted.
What scene?
A guy went crazy in the center of
the city, shot dead three guys
at the scene in broad daylight and then fled.
We don't know,
Why wasn't I informed about that?
They weren't related. He used a 38. No
There were pennies. He was an amateur.
Who were the victims?
Some mafia pawns and a fat waiter.
Oh, wonderful. All criminals
from quiet Boston they begin to
look dead and you think they are not
related. Greenly, the day you want
Let the Boston police think for me,
I will have a tag on my toe.
Now get me a patrol car and take me there.
I want photos of the crime scene and
witness statements.
[Music]
A fucking gunslinger.
Looks like we're dealing with a cowboy.
A river towards you
that will always be crowded with souls.
In the name of the Father and of the Son and of the
Holy Spirit.
And, listen, you have to teach me that prayer.
I really like that [ __ ]
Calm down, Rock. It's a family prayer.
My grandfather taught it to my father and it is something
our.
Let's go.
The victims were found in a room
strip club. Those murders and
three others linked to the mafia
that happened in this Boston cafe
This very afternoon they raise the bill
six dead today alone. There is no doubt
that the victims were criminals. That
perhaps explains why citizens
They did not ask for these to be stopped
crimes.
These two crime scenes are
related. Too many coincidences.
They are the same thing separated by 5 hours.
There are dead mobsters in both scenes.
But,
Why did he kill the waiter?
A crime of passion drove him mad,
He shot everyone here. He ran out
reply.
Does this look like a [ __ ] office to you?
mail? This guy came here with a
intention. I wouldn't know exactly what it was about
to do, but I had a good idea, didn't I?
The waiter's incident was no accident.
Well, they didn't help us much.
let's say. Many people saw it, but no one
wants to talk.
Of course.
Oh, God.
They're not seeing the pattern here.
We have important questions in the
crime scenes, but there are no
answers.
Why did they kill the guys in the
other two booths? Why did they kill the
waiter?
[ __ ]
I hate clueless lasenas.
I'd better get out of here.
Do me a favor. Let me know next time.
maybe because these guys haven't yet
they finished.
[Music]
Augustos de Stefano, former second-in-command,
Yacabeta family, retired position.
Rot,
Augustos. I need your help. I have a
very serious problem. I'm not joking.
I need the shower.
Maximum security prison.
[Music]
The Duke.
What did you do,
Roco, a messenger.
I could wipe out the entire mafia.
East Coast if he decided to declare for the
state. It can destroy us brick by brick
brick.
But for now he is content, killing us.
One by one and what is worse, he does it very
GOOD.
Listen to me, I hope you understand with
who are you dealing with. This guy is from
fear.
When I was little, my dad used to talk about
him as if he were a ghost.
Move it.
Your father and I used it three times in 20
years, only when things were going well
all fucked up.
Whenever we needed to kill one of
ours, we called this guy.
He liked to kill mobsters.
I only had one rule, no women or
children.
Believe me, you shouldn't use this guy.
unless you are 100% sure that
you need. He's a fucking monster. Just
There's a problem. He's been in jail for 25 or
30 years old. I don't even know if he's still alive or
if you can do it.
Prisoner number 6570534.
Sentence: 25 years to life in prison.
Well, there is a way to fix it.
Find her.
Parole granted.
Okay. Let's get to the point. I know a
undesirable bastard who makes everyone
others look like altar boys.
It was the worst night of my life when
I knew this. He never told me a thing
[ __ ] word. We drove for 25
minutes. He neither sighed nor cleared his voice,
nothing.
Yes, what you say about dad has a lot to do with it.
sense, imbecile.
Yes, as always so idiotic.
His expression was blank, there was no
nothing. The guy killed an entire family,
to the wife, the children, to everyone, as if
I was ordering a [ __ ] pizza.
The house is messy.
I knew that if I didn't calm down he would kill me.
[Music]
The bastard plays poker at home with
a group of mobsters every Saturday.
That was the worst day of my life.
OK that's fine.
Don't worry, Rock. We'll take care of it.
and you will feel better.
Jack, pass me the briefcase.
Give me a minute.
[Music]
Very good,
this is what happened.
They waited
in a parked car for the child
came out.
Here it goes.
They entered through the garage. The boy said that
leaves it open when you go out
bicycle.
[Music]
Did you know that the wife is the guardian?
Know the code.
Enter the code. Come on, enter the [ __ ]
code. I swear I'll kill you.
Hey, his hands are tied.
Hey, why do you always touch my
women?
The wife said she doesn't remember what
It happened after I put in the code.
Remember that it faded away, but by the
burn on the back. I think they used
a discharge gun.
This guy knew his friend was coming to
play poker and they knew that the
door could only be opened from
inside. So they waited and when the
door opened, heavens,
nobody expected that.
[Music]
Panic, devastation was like shooting at
fish in a [ __ ] fish tank.
to everyone.
[Music]
These guys jumped under the
table. The trajectory of the bullet
It shows that he came right from the front. That
It means that one of the murderers is
knelt down.
[Music]
Something went wrong right here.
Shit, [ __ ] isn't here. What do you mean?
He is not here, [ __ ] He is not here.
Why don't you look again, [ __ ] I
I know perfectly well what it's like.
Look behind you.
Ah, son of a
Oh, [ __ ]
No, no, no, no. Damn it! Let it out.
Let it go. Ah, let it go. Ah, [ __ ]
It's time to earn your place, Rock.
will kill, [ __ ] It was your [ __ ] idea that was
would unite.
One of these guys is a real one.
psychopath. I met this man. I wanted
that he suffered.
Okay, Rock, es
Now. Kill him already. I don't want to die.
[Music]
Damn
from [ __ ] You killed him.
Very good,
[ __ ] [ __ ]
Take a deep breath, [ __ ] You did it
Good. You did very well, brother.
[Music]
They left through the street door. No
They had no idea what was in store for them.
Now they had six guys in front of them
pointing at them.
It was an [ __ ] ambush.
It was like dropping a [ __ ] bomb on
the center of a city.
For a few seconds,
This place was the Apocalypse.
Ah, there was a shooting.
[Music]
Are
Son of [ __ ]
[Music]
Ah.
Mar, are you okay, son of a [ __ ]
R, grab the [ __ ] bag.
[ __ ]
Erase the blood. Erase the blood.
Erase the blood.
Oh my.
Grab the bag at once. [ __ ] finger.
[ __ ]
made by a single guy with six guns.
Why don't you let me think, Genño?
And why do they take so many samples?
blood?
I can't get a good sample.
There is a variable here that I am not
seeing.
They used ammonia.
None of this is useful, [ __ ] Do you know what?
What does that mean? Even though we have
suspects in the case, we have no
evidence. Nothing, nothing. [ __ ] Who
what the hell are they?
I have never seen anything like this in my entire life.
[ __ ] life. Who [ __ ] are they?
Who?
[ __ ] was red. I know you know that, so
don't lie to me.
To [ __ ] I told you I never did before
had seen,
but I did know you.
To [ __ ] To [ __ ] Both of them.
Why don't you tell the truth, Roco? Tell me.
who [ __ ] that guy.
Now [ __ ] mother. You are a [ __ ]
liar.
Victoria.
[Music]
[Applause]
You
[Music]
I'm sure the research
will lead to the capture of the suspects.
Thank you,
[ __ ]
What? That guy
He's the guy who got us out of the way with what
by Jacob.
And that guy is very smart. They have nothing.
That kind of truth knows, sooner or later
He will discover us early.
I believe he will.
Well, I'd say that makes it a
[ __ ] problem.
Don't touch him. He's a good man.
Okay, whatever you want.
[Music]
No, it can't be.
David de la Rock.
I didn't see it.
[Music]
You've had enough to drink. I'm sure you want to.
Pour me another drink, [ __ ] [ __ ]
That
does it stink?
Understand,
This thing about going to mass in the morning must
end.
We have to go in the morning. Now we are
fugitives.
[Music]
pi
No.
You will do what you are told
I'm so sorry you have to see this.
Don't look at me. Shut up and close the [ __ ]
boca.
I'm doing this for him now. Open
That's it, Father. Open up. But I'll kill you.
same.
May God have mercy on my soul.
Damn idiot. Let him go. I'll kill you now.
same, [ __ ]
Okay, just calm down. It can hurt us,
Brother. He can ruin all this.
Let it out, you crazy man. Or I swear I'll
bush.
You won't. You won't. Conarme
want.
It's there. Yes, yes, my son. Tell me.
Do your job, father, and don't mess up.
this.
How long has it been since you confessed,
Heavens?
I never went to confession.
I came to seek advice, not the
salvation.
Why did you come to a church for a
advice if you are not religious?
It's my ethic.
I put wicked men in jail.
But the law is full of procedures
bureaucratic and loopholes that make
These bastards drain. I found out that
There are two types who settle accounts with
iron fist, as if they had the
God's permission.
God's permission. God does not give permission.
in these times. I think what they do
It is necessary. I feel it is right.
The soul is what allows us to feel.
It is like a conduit through which the
Lord speaks to us.
Today you felt that you would find the
answers here in the house of the Lord
and you feel
that these men are necessary.
So the Lord has spoken to you twice
today.
Really,
You came into this church talking about
what you believe and what you feel. It's so
hard to believe that God has brought you
here.
I guess not.
It's very easy to be scathing about religion,
but it is much more difficult to be firm.
I want to defend what I believe in,
Father. First you must know what you believe in.
I think these young people are right.
You know them personally.
Yeah.
They would hurt an innocent person for
some reason.
No, they would never do that.
Well, not the two Irishmen. The
Italian is perhaps a bit of an idiot.
I'm getting it now.
All the things I wish I could do,
they already do them.
What should I do?
Because I am a man who must defend
the law.
Divine laws
are above the law
of man.
Yes, that's what I was thinking. No, no, no.
was feeling. He just needs that
you say so.
Amen.
I will help them.
Forgive me, father.
Thank you, Father.
One way or the other.
Amen.
Bye bye.
Listen to me well, Dominus Ominus or whatever
sea. Remember, you are obligated. You cannot
talk about this with anyone.
Get out of this church.
The Lord works in mysterious ways,
¿no?
What does it mean?
Answer.
That's all you can say.
The light illuminated half of his face. It seemed
who had a gray beard about 50 and
so many 60 years.
Are you telling me that he was a guy with
six guns and was a person of the
old age?
We better find him before he
find us again. I'll see what I can do.
do. How do I
contact you? We'll kill Papay this
night in the comfort of your own
home. We're going to New York. It's just that
this place is getting dangerous.
Careful.
Okay. I'll call you tonight.
I feel like I'm alive.
Yes, but it isn't.
I don't know where it is. Nobody knows. The
Duke is a damn Judini. He disappears.
Why did you bring it then?
Need someone from outside.
This Roco guy is smart. He knows everyone.
the world. I would recognize our thugs
immediately.
Just for him. The messenger
is the one that is killing all of our
men. He's not afraid of her. He says he's
Well. He has all the thugs in the
city.
At home. I don't know what's going on, but he has
something to do with this man.
Oh, [ __ ]
We got them. They tried to get in through the
basement.
How many?
Three.
Unfortunate.
Where [ __ ] do you want to go?
[ __ ]
Where do you want to go?
Leave me alone.
Call me.
Calm down, boys, calm down, calm down.
Red,
sit down.
Do you have any answers for me? No.
Yeah.
Rock, Rock, mírame, mírame. Rock, Rock,
Look at me, look at me. Ro, look at me, Ro. Ro, you go
you're going to be okay. Ro, you're going to be okay.
Calm down. Calm down.
OK.
What do you think, guys?
These guys are tough.
I believe her, [ __ ]
Yes, they will not speak in any way.
I know Roko. He's not smart at all.
The other two are the brain. He is a
pawn
He's an idiot.
There's just one thing to do.
[Music]
God, no.
[ __ ]
Rock, rock. No, no, no.
Ro, no,
no. Rock.
You can't stop me. Get out of here and
never stop.
[Music]
No, no. Rock,
son of [ __ ]
Sons of [ __ ] I'm going to kill you, sons of
[ __ ]
Hey, boss.
Yes, Chapi.
I don't mean to be disrespectful, but I think
that we forgot something. Hilde said. It's a
[ __ ] animal, will not stop until it kills
someone. I guarantee you this now. He
think that this is not over.
Damn!
No,
But why? Why? Uh, why?
has to continue, [ __ ]
Yes, he believes his work is not yet done.
That bastard must be in the bushes.
now.
I'm leaving.
You four, stay here and
take care of him.
[Music]
he's just a guy.
At [ __ ] full.
Why the big deal? Do it.
[Music]
I'll go back down to take care of those.
fools.
[Music]
That [ __ ]
Hello,
I live, he sent me
to entertain them.
Sorry, babe. Can't make it tonight.
be. The [ __ ] is splashing hard,
you understand?
[Music]
That live is great. He always sends us the
better. God.
[Music]
OK.
Let's go.
Come here.
What are you doing,
Old? I haven't done it in weeks. It's been 5
minutes.
Hurry up.
Come with mommy. How dirty.
Come to Mommy. Come, come, baby.
Do you want to do it with the champion?
No, boy.
Okay. Let's do it ringside.
Love,
come, baby, come.
Do you want to see the champion?
Come on, honey.
Yes baby.
That [ __ ]
That's it,
that's it.
It's time.
[Music]
It's about time.
Hey, babe. What's two for one?
[Music]
Shepherd, shepherdess, we will be for you,
for you, my Lord, for you.
By your hand,
your hand gave us power.
That we may carry out your orders with
readiness.
A river will flow to you, which is crowded
of soul will always be there.
In the name of the Father, and of the Son, and of the
Holy Spirit.
[Music]
3 months later.
He will be prosecuted today for the third time in 2
years. Inside is the infamous boss of the
mafia, Papa Joya Jaqueva, and will testify
against the accusations of his
participation in the murders of no
less than 17 men. The case of the State
It is based mainly on evidence
circumstantial against him and it is expected
a third acquittal. It will never happen
will shed the blood of the innocent,
but the blood of the wicked will flow
like a river.
The three will open their black wings and will be
God's vengeful hammer.
Ah, I was with my mother, we were in the
I fill the butcher shop, because on Thursdays
cook gnokis for
Madam Beta,
behave yourself in this room.
Lawyer, go ahead.
He has a lot of charisma. He's the next John
Cats.
He will be released even with this evidence.
Look, the people of Yacabeta are at the
left and the families of men
that killed the right. Everyone wants
justice.
No, I didn't know where I was.
Look at it.
He doesn't look worried.
He will be free.
You guys back.
Turn off the [ __ ] camera.
They have their weapons up there. One to the
time. Now
she was running.
No. Where does it take me? What does it do?
What is he doing back?
No,
you have been chosen
to reveal our existence to the
world.
You will witness what will happen here.
today and then they will tell it.
Look over here everyone. Now it's a good
moment to
Crack.
You must look, dear.
It will all be over soon.
[Music]
Let's go.
Now you will receive us.
We do not ask you for the poor or the
hungry.
We don't want the elderly or the sick.
It is the corrupt ones we are demanding.
It is evil that we are looking for.
As long as we live we will hunt them.
Every day we will shed his blood
until it rains from the skies. No
kill, don't rape, don't steal. They are
principles that can be embraced by
men of all religions.
They are not kind suggestions, they are codes
of conduct and those who ignore them
they will pay the most expensive way.
Evil has several degrees. We urge
the lesser miserable ones who do not
push the limits and go over to the side of
the great corruption until now
domain. Because if they do, one day
They will look behind you and see you
the three of you. And that day you
will repent
and we will send them with the God who
wish.
Shepherds for you, my Lord, for you of
your hand consists of power. draw yours with
soon a river we will flow towards
tiado will be in the name of the Father and
of the Son
and of the Holy Spirit. Did you see
[Applause]
[Music]
what happened?
Yes, it was there.
Until
where will we get with this?
The question is not how far.
The question is whether you have the character
and deep faith
to get as far as necessary.
After the amazing surveillance for
Police at Jack Beda's trial yesterday
the largest search operation has begun
that is remembered to capture the three
men whom the press has dubbed the
Saints. I went out to the street to find out
What do you think of the three of them?
Can anyone take a gun and kill?
someone just because you think they are
doing something good?
I don't have an opinion.
They make this world safer.
Jokes.
It's for a good cause. They only kill
good people cause. Why don't you
are you listening? This will lead to something much worse.
I don't agree.
Well, I think you're naive.
I love the saints. They are
doing very well. Let them continue. Finish with
the murderers in the streets.
They don't kill just for fame.
They want to become famous.
They should be in big cities.
In major cities.
May God do all this.
religion. Who do they think they are?
son?
Of course I believe in the death penalty. Yes
If they left me, I would execute them.
Catch them and kill them. Oh, I support you.
To [ __ ] the children of [ __ ] The more
people kill, it will be better for everyone. That
It's what you deserve.
No, don't say that, cuel, because no
you know nothing.
I'm in, man. Hey, I'm in.
Do you understand? Where can I join?
Who are they to be judges?
No. What if your mother sees you?
No comments.
I fear for myself, I fear for my children. I have
fear of walking on the street.
I can't believe you're saying that. It's a
madness. Listen to yourself.
Listen to yourself.
I think they just like killing people.
No comments. Nothing to comment on.
I have nothing to say. Thank you.
All this commotion in the press,
you make the problem worse.
You give them power. By putting me in the
microphone in the face, give more power to
the saints.
I don't want to talk about it.
No, really, I don't want to talk about that.
If you enter a child's room, there
will be. Batman, Superman and
also the Saints.
It keeps you awake at night, my dear, because
You know what, it doesn't take away from me.
No comments. They are
No, old man, don't talk to them. Let's go.
Don't talk to them. I'm willing to
everything, [ __ ] Okay. I'm ready to
do it too, you know? I'm willing
to do it.
[Music]